<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linux on New Linux User</title>
    <link>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linux on New Linux User</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Linux: Unveiling the Best Attributes for Your Computing Needs</title>
      <link>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/blog/linux_vs_windowsos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/blog/linux_vs_windowsos/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of the constant battle between Windows and macOS users, each proclaiming the superiority of their operating system? If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for an alternative that offers a unique set of advantages, Linux might be the answer you&amp;rsquo;ve been searching for. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the best attributes of using Linux over Windows and macOS.
Freedom and Open Source Philosophy: Linux is built on the principles of open source software, which means that anyone can view, modify, and distribute its source code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Uncharted Waters of Universal Blue</title>
      <link>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/blog/ublue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/blog/ublue/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As a newcomer to the vast universe of Linux, I&amp;#39;ve often found myself feeling like a voyager lost at sea, struggling to decipher the complexities and intricacies that this open-source world entails. My knowledge and skills are admittedly limited, and my ability to articulate the technical nuances of Universal Blue (U-Blue) remains far from realization. However, despite my novice status, I can unequivocally share my profound impressions of the performance, stability, and transformative aura that U-Blue brings to Fedora Silverblue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resolving Zoom Screen Sharing and Custom Backgrounds</title>
      <link>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/blog/flatseal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/blog/flatseal/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#39;ve found your way here, you might be facing the same challenges I did with Zoom on Linux. Don&amp;#39;t worry; I&amp;#39;ve got the perfect solution for you, and it&amp;#39;s called Flatseal. This incredible tool not only resolved my Zoom screen sharing and custom background issues but also made configuring applications from Flathub a breeze.
The Quest to Optimize Zoom on Linux As a tech enthusiast who frequently relies on Zoom for meetings and collaboration, I encountered two significant hurdles when using the Flatpak version of Zoom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Static Website on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/projects/hugo-static-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/projects/hugo-static-website/</guid>
      <description>Creating a static website with Hugo and hosting it on GitHub can seem daunting, but I&amp;rsquo;ll break it down into simple steps that beginners can follow. By the end of this post, you&amp;rsquo;ll have your static website up and running. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started: Step 1: Install Hugo
First, you need to install Hugo, a popular static site generator. You can download it from the official website at Hugo Themes. Follow the installation instructions for your specific operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Linux</title>
      <link>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new-linux-user.streamers.city/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Switching To Linux Switching to Linux has been an incredible journey for me, and it&amp;#39;s been full of valuable experiences and encounters with the Linux community. While it&amp;#39;s true that the Linux community can be quite opinionated at times, especially among the Arch base enthusiasts, I&amp;#39;ve also found that it&amp;#39;s a place where you can discover a wealth of knowledge and connect with people who are eager to help you learn and solve problems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
